clicksmob.com 2017-11-15

# ClicksMob | Privacy Policy

ClicksMob, Inc (hereinafter: "ClicksMob" or the "Company") respect the interest that visitors to our websites have in understanding what information is collected electronically, how it is collected, to whom it is or may be disclosed and how it is used.

### IMPORTANT LIMITATIONS TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY

— This policy applies only to information collected on websites that are directly linked to this policy, and does not apply to information collected in other areas, whether online or offline. This policy does not apply to third-party websites that may be accessed through a link from a site covered by this policy. You should review the privacy policies of any third-party websites to understand how that site collects, uses and discloses any Personal Information or non-Personal Information.

— This policy does not apply to information collected through applications on mobile or personal devices, even if the application may be accessed through a link from a site covered by this policy.

### COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

"Personal Information" is information that directly identifies you or could reasonably be used in combination with other information to identify you and which is submitted to and/or collected by ClicksMob web sites and maintained by or for ClicksMob in an accessible form. Examples of Personal Information that directly identify you can include your name, social security number, generic data, street address, telephone number, email address and other similar information. Examples of Personal Information that when combined with other information may be able to identify you include race, gender, zip code and other similar information. Both types of information are considered "Personal Information" for the purposes of this policy.

Please do not submit any Personal Information if you do not want it to be collected. You should be aware, however, that without providing requested information, even Personal Information, and you may not be able to participate in particular features or activities that require such information.

We do not collect any Personal Information unless it is provided to us voluntarily through forms or data fields. Certain areas of our websites allow you to contact us to ask questions or provide comments or other information. Please be aware that when you ask questions or provide comments or other information, you may be disclosing Personal Information.

### HOW PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE USED

If you provide us with Personal Information we may use that information to contact you by e-mail, regular mail, telephone or other means, to provide you with information you requested about specific products or services, provide additional future information about products or services that may be of interest to you. Other or additional information about use of your Personal Information may appear at the point where you are asked to provide Personal Information in a form or data field.

We use this consolidated information to help us better design and promote ClicksMob's products, to communicate information to you, to enhance our marketing andactivities, and to facilitate other business functions.

### WHO PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE DISCLOSED TO

ClicksMob will not transfer or allow access to your Personal Information to third parties (ii) to Advertisers who assist us in providing service to you; (iii) in connection with security related or law enforcement investigations or in the course of cooperating with authorities; (iv) to comply with legal requirements or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (v) when we believe it is necessary to share information in order to assist in an investigation regarding, or to prevent, illegal activities, suspected fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person; and (vi) to third parties with whom ClicksMob is jointly marketing a product or service or jointly conducting a program or activity.

### SECURITY

ClicksMob takes reasonable precautions to keep Personal Information secure against unauthorized access and use. However, the confidentiality of personal information transmitted over the Internet cannot be guaranteed. ClicksMob cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will not gain access to your Personal Information; therefore, when submitting personal information to ClicksMob websites, you must weigh both the benefits and the risks.

### COLLECTION OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

Non-Personal Information is information that is not personal, such as questions, comments, ideas and suggestions that you provide, or information that we may collect that is not linked to any Personal Information. Non-Personal Information will be treated as non-confidential, and we may disclose and/or use that information without any obligation whatsoever to you, for any purpose and through any means.

ClicksMob websites may use a tracking technology called a "cookie." A "cookie" is a small text file that a website can place on your computer's hard drive in order, for example, to collect information about your activities on the site, to track your preferences and selections. Cookies may be placed on your computer by ClicksMob (a "first party cookie") or by another company or advertiser that ClicksMob engages to provide services or advertising on a ClicksMob website (a "third party cookie").

### HOW TO STOP GETTING COMMUNICATIONS

If you decide you no longer wish to receive information or communications about particular products and services, or from ClicksMob (for example, emails and telephone calls), you may opt out of any particular product or service or from all mailings by contacting us at the following toll-free number: 1-866-285-5245. You may click on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any ClicksMob email and follow the directions that appear on the screen in order to opt out of communications from ClicksMob.  
Please note that you may continue to receive materials for a period of time while our lists are being updated.

### HOW MAY I CORRECT OR DELETE PERSONAL INFORMATION?

You may request that we remove your Personal Information from our current customer records or that we amend your Personal Information. Please notify us by contact us.

### UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Without prejudice to your rights under applicable law, ClicksMob reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy without prior notice to reflect technological advancements, legal and regulatory changes and good business practices. If ClicksMob changes its privacy practices, an updated version of this Privacy Policy will reflect those changes and we will notify you of such changes by updating the effective date at the top of this Privacy Policy.  
Thank you for your interest in ClicksMob, Inc.
